=== Plugin Name ===

Plugin Name: GMO Font Agent
Plugin URI: 
Author: WP Shop byGMO
Author URI: http://www.wpshop.com
Contributors: WP Shop byGMO
Donation Link: 
Tags: Slider, Simple, Effects
Requires at least: 3.8.1
Tested up to: 3.9 Beta
Stable tag: Version 1.0 
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

== Description ==

GMO Font Agent plugin is tied up with Google fonts, gives you a choice to use variety of stylish web fonts.  The plugin is genericon and IcoMoon compatible, to enhance its usability.  It can be inserted from the post editor.  This is simply a plug and play for everyone.


== Instruction ==

GMO Font Agent plugin is equipped with following features. 

-Google font integration 
-Custom fonts can be used on body, heading 1-6, Contents, GMO Showtime-Caption (Caption shown when GMO Showtime slider is used) only. 
-Icon font generation (http://genericons.com/#pinterest-alt), Integration with free version of IcoMoon (http://icomoon.io/#icons) 


Basic Settings
1. Install plugin and activate.  Open [GMO Font Agent] after activating. 
2. Open [Google Font API Key], and enter Googole Font API Key
3. Open [Font Settings] to change font size for desired area. 
* This class configuration is only used to apply slider caption font changes with 'GMO Showtime' plugin.

How to Set Icon Fonts
* Simply activate a plugin to get started.  No initial set up required. 

1. Find a [Iconfonts by GMO Font Agent] button in the posts/pages edit screen. Button is located on top left of the textarea when visual editor is selected.
2. Click [Iconfonts by GMO Font Agent] to find a list of icon fonts. 
3. Choose an icon font type from the pull-down menu, select icon and click [Insert] button.
 

== Installation ==

Search and download plugin from either WordPress admin page or http://wordpress.org/plugins.  From the WordPress admin page, simply activate the plugin, or upload a file from "Add New" to install and activate plug-in.  

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

== Changelog == 

-Initial Release

== Upgrade Notice ==

== Screenshots ==
screenshot-1.png

